indfy.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy

By accessing http://www.indfy.com ("this Website"), you ("the User") are giving your consent to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by this Website from time to time.

http://www.indfy.com (hereinafter referred to as "This Website" or "the Website") respects your privacy and committed to ensure that your privacy is protected by means of protecting your Personally Identifiable Information you share with this Website. Personally Identifiable Information is information by which a person can be identified such as name, address, telephone number, SSN, e – mail ID, date of birth, Credit card information etc. Personally Identifiable Information may be received from the Users of this Website.

Should this Website ask you to provide Personally Identifiable Information when using the website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

This Website may without any notice or reason, update this privacy policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are comfortable with any changes. This policy was last updated on February 2nd 2011.

**What This Website Collects**

  * This Website may collect Personally Identifiable Information
  * This Website may use 'cookies' and 'web beacons' to manage your status and verify your identity
  * Website may collect geophysical IP Address/ Browser Information/ Other Technical Information for system and server administration.
  * Website may collect other information relevant to surveys and offers.

**What does This Website do with the information collected.**

This Website requires these information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: To fulfill the services you have asked this Website to perform

  * For internal record keeping.
  * To improve this Website products and services.
  * To use in the User's Profile Page and similar features on the Website
  * This Website may periodically send promotional e-mail about new products, special offers or other information which the Website think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. However, you may unsubscribe yourself to such promotional e–mails through the link provided in every such e–mail itself or by replying the e–mail with the Subject - "Unsubscribe" or "Removal Request".
  * This Website may use the information to customize the website according to your interests

**With whom This Website shares the information**

As a thumb rule, This Website will not willfully disclose your Personally Identifiable Information with any third party except under following conditions-

  * When Information is forwarded to Service Providers to fulfill the services you have asked This Website to perform.
  * When This Website is legally compelled to provide the information to the Law Enforcement Authorities or government regulatory or administrative or similar agency as part of a judicial or administrative proceeding to disclose the Information.

**Security**

This Website is committed to ensure that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure the Website has put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information the Website collects online. While the Website strives to protect your personal information, it can not ensure or warrant total security of any information you transmit over the transmission medium.

**Limitation of Liability**

This Website may contain links to other websites or advertisements which drive you to another website. However, once you have used these links to leave the Website, you should note that the Website does not have any control over that other website. Therefore, the Website cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites as such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the Privacy Policy applicable to the website in question.

Last Updated On: **2011/07/11**
